thefryecompany.com 2016-06-04

# Privacy Policy | FRYE

## Privacy Policy

We, at Frye, value your privacy. We do not share or sell your information to third parties. thefryecompany.com allows you to buy Frye products, enter occasional contests, receive special discounts, fill out surveys, and receive newsletters, e-mails and other promotional information from us.

We use the information that we collect about you exclusively to fulfill your purchases and to create a more personalized online experience. This policy may change from time to time. All changes will be posted on thefryecompany.com as indicated in Section 9 below.

Frye is a division of Jimlar. Only Jimlar will collect, maintain or use your information.

### Information

### Types of Information

In order to better provide you with products and services, thefryecompany.com collects two types of information about its visitors: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth and customized experience while using thefryecompany.com.

In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order.

### Personally Identifiable Information

This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. Personal information is requested when you order a product or service, enter contests or sweepstakes, fill out surveys, and send us feedback. For example, this information might include your name, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit/debit card or other payment information, and product details. With this information, we can fill your orders, and better provide you with personalized services.

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. thefryecompany.com gathers certain information about you based upon where you shop on it in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis.

For example, this information may include the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the website from which you came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the World Wide Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination.

In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet, browse and shop.

### Product Reviews

If you choose to submit a product review on thefryecompany.com, we may ask you for information such as your name and city of residence, which may be used in connection with your review (altogether, the “Review Information”). By submitting the Review Information, you consent to our use, modification, reproduction, transmission, publication and display of such Review Information on thefryecompany.com and also in connection with the promotion, marketing and advertising of our products and services; however, we are under no obligation to post any Review Information.

### Information Sharing

Only Jimlar maintains and may use your information. It is not shared with any other third parties with the exception of third party companies such as credit/debit card processing centers, and shipping carriers employed by Jimlar to perform functions on its behalf including order fulfillment, postal and email delivery, and credit processes. The only information shared is that information which is necessary to process your order.

We reserve the right to disclose your information as required by law, and when we believe disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us.

## Methods

### Shopping

thefryecompany.com collects information from visitors to its site regarding the URLs they came from, domain types (e.g., .com or .org), their IP addresses, the date and time of their visit or order, the number of visits and orders, the number of visits per browsing session, the operating system and browser type used to come to the site, the country, state, and telephone area code where their servers are located, the pages and page titles of its site that visitors viewed during their visit, whether the visitor's computer is enabled for Java or cookies, browser language, applications, and plug-ins, and any search terms entered on thefryecompany.com.

### Ordering

When you order from thefryecompany.com, it collects personally identifiable information from you. If you order one of our products or services, thefryecompany.com will collect and maintain your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit/debit card or other payment information, order number, referring URL, IP address, page you bought from and a password. It collects this, and other information, as disclosed in this policy, in order to fill your order, to communicate with you about your order, and possibly to send you promotional materials. Before confirming your order, you will have the opportunity to review the product order form and make changes and additions to the information it contained and these changes will be automatically kept for future use.

### Online Surveys and Polling

In order to improve our services to you, we may ask some of our customers to voluntarily complete surveys. Individual survey answers are confidential, although only non-personally identifiable information is collected. If you do not wish to participate in a survey, simply decline to participate when asked.

### Contests and Sweepstakes

If we should hold a contest or sweepstakes and you opt to enter, thefryecompany.com may ask you for contact information such as your name, address, and e-mail address in order to administer the contest, to send you promotional e-mails, notify winners and make the winners’ list publicly available pursuant to applicable laws. Your consent to such promotional use and disclosure of this information is a condition of your participation.

As a condition of receiving any prize, you will be required to submit an Affidavit of Eligibility, for us to ensure that you are eligible to receive the prize according to the Contest Rules.

### Newsletters & Promotional E-mails

Periodically, we may offer free newsletters, and promotional e-mails as a service to our customers. These newsletters and e-mails will be sent to you via e-mail and will contain information on how to opt out of future newsletters and promotional e-mails.

### Contact Information

If you contact our Customer Service representatives by telephone, e-mail or letter, we may keep a record of your correspondence or comments. If you report a problem with thefryecompany.com, we may collect such information in a file specific to you. If you contact us through our feedback area or by calling one of our customer service representatives, we may ask for your name, e-mail address and order information in order to send you a reply.

### Cookies

When you use thefryecompany.com, it may store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use. A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer’s hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to thefryecompany.com.

thefryecompany.com cookies store randomly assigned user identification numbers, the country where you are located, and your first name to welcome you back to thefryecompany.com. The cookies make your use of thefryecompany.com easier, allow you to retrieve an earlier shopping cart, make thefryecompany.com run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. You will be unable to shop on thefryecompany.com without your browser set to accept cookies.

## Options

### Security

When you access your account information, the information is kept on a secure server. All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access by physical security means.

### Updating Personally Identifiable Information

You have the ability to access and edit the personal information that you have provided to thefryecompany.com. During the online ordering process you can review, change or delete the information that you have submitted. You may change any of your personal information in your account online at any time. We encourage you to promptly update your information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past purchases, you cannot delete information associated with past purchases.

Also, as a security measure we "back up" the data stored on our systems, and such prior information cannot be completely removed from our databases. As a result, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our backed-up databases.

### Promotional E-mails

We may from time to time send you e-mail or other communications regarding current promotions, specials and new additions to thefryecompany.com. You may "opt-out," or unsubscribe from our newsletters by following the unsubscribe instructions in any e-mail you receive from us, or by sending an e-mail to [Frye-Privacy@thefryecompany.com](mailto:Frye-Privacy@thefryecompany.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).

After doing so, you will not receive future promotional emails unless they open a new account, enter a contest, or sign up to receive newsletters or emails. Please allow up to 2 weeks to process your request.

### Policy Changes

This Privacy Policy was last changed in November 2006. If we make changes to any terms or conditions of the Privacy Policy, the changes will be posted in this document which is always located on thefryecompany.com. We may change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless stated otherwise.

### Children's Policy

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act took effect on April 21, 2000 and imposes certain requirements on websites directed toward children under 13, that collect information on those children, or websites that know they are collecting information on children under the age of 13.

We do NOT sell products for purchase by children under 13 through thefryecompany.com. Youth-oriented products are sold for purchase by adults only. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Frye is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children.

Love your Fryes or send them back for a full refund,

completely free, within 30 days.*

* * *

Click here for pre-paid return labels and to learn more about our

return policy and repair program.

***Free returns valid on US orders only.**

### Thank you for signing up for our newsletter!

For a tailored experience (and a birthday treat!),   
tell us more about you...
